dignews.com 2010-05-12

# Privacy Policy | Digital Entertainment News

## Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
General Information

Digital Entertainment News is an online publication, updated daily, providing news, information and services related to the world of digital entertainment. Digital Entertainment News respects and understands the importance of the privacy of our readers. This policy applies to all sections of Digital Entertainment News (http://www.dignews.com)

Collected Data  
Digital Entertainment News collects your information in order to better provide information and services. Upon entering Digital Entertainment News, certain information is collected by our servers.

This information may include, but may not be limited to, the location or website from which you came; the location from which you left, the time you spend on parts of Digital Entertainment News; the operating system used (i.e., Windows 98, Win XP, etc.); the software used to browse Digital Entertainment News (Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape, etc.); and your IP address.

Your IP address is a number designated by your Internet Service Provider that identifies the account you are using to access the Internet with your Internet Service Provider, and/or the Internet Service Provider you are using to access the Internet itself. This data collection is standard and common to most websites on the Internet.

The standard data we collect is not personally identifiable information – it does not identify you as an individual. None of this information will be disclosed in any form unless otherwise stated.

By any of using Digital Entertainment News’ services or reading its content, you agree that you understand the nature this data collection. Digital Entertainment News will not knowingly retain and/or disclose this standard data other than in an aggregate form, including, but not limited to, demographic data averages (stat tracking).

Personal User Data  
The only ways in which Digital Entertainment News may receive personally identifiable information about you is if you knowingly and willingly provide it. This can happen in a number of ways, such as entering and registering for the forum, or participating in various contests. This information is submitted willfully, and done to facilitate a level of service (such as awarding prizes, message boards) that would otherwise not be possible.

Digital Entertainment News may share the aggregate results of the data it receives, with advertisers and partners to help them better understand our services and their opportunities, although we will not disclose personal data.

Protection  
No computer system is one hundred per cent protected. While normally safe and in a secure area, the information that Digital Entertainment News collects, like any other data anywhere, could unlawfully be retrieved by a third party. Digital Entertainment News makes every effort to ensure that submitted data is not intercepted, we cannot guarantee that this will be the case.

Recourses  
Readers that would rather not provide any of the user data requested by our registration process do not need to register with us. You can still view much of the content and use many of the services offered by our sites without registering. Opting not to register for the forums or newsletter will result in no personal information being submitted to Digital Entertainment News.

At any time, you may contact us at info@digitalentertainmentnews.com and un-register to any subscription service you may have registered for.

Children, Parents and the Internet  
Although Digital Entertainment News does not primarily have content directed to children below the age of thirteen (13), we welcome readers of all ages. We do, however specifically request that those readers have parent/guardian permission before taking part in any services. Digital Entertainment News cannot be held responsible for any information received or disclosed by our readers.

Digital Entertainment News respects and encourages parental involvement in a child’s internet usage and readership. If a parent wishes for a child to be removed from any and/or all Digital Entertainment News services, please send an email specifically requesting your wish to info@digitalentertainmentnews.com. Digital Entertainment News however, cannot and will not be held responsible for access to our services any child may subsequently gain, as this is beyond our realm of control.

Questions  
Any questions regarding this privacy statement should be directed to:  
Digital Entertainment News  
121 NW 82nd St  
Seattle, WA 98117  
info@digitalentertainmentnews.com

Every message will be read, and actions taken where necessary.

Updated September 2003
